EnergySage, Inc. Boston, MA

Belmont Wheelworks Belmont, MA

Applied Innovation Inc. Dublin, OH

Then been writing and using software to solve problems for one 15 years, I was not encloded offware requires for them upon, then the he dealty in 2005 to pursue proposition offered. I was a formation to find at a large bide date, when I eighted the filter of a validary looke, from solling biles to administrating coffware. In 2014, I made the soll in the problems of the contract of the original and the problems of the contract of the problems of the problems

Adapting, Analysing, Asimilating, Coding, Communicating, Debugging, Editing, Epighaining, Programming, Researching, Teaching, Todaleshooting, Software Development Development Psycon, Toxascript, SQL, GI, Linu, Units, Data Engineering, Teat-Orient Development, Virtual Machines, Communicating, Debugging, Editing, Epighaining, Programming, Researching, Teaching, Toxascript, SQL, GI, Linu, Units, Data Engineering, Teat-Orient Development, Virtual Machines, Communicating, Debugging, Editing, Epighaining, Programming, Researching, Teaching, Toxascript, SQL, GI, Linu, Units, Data Engineering, Teat-Orient Development, Virtual Machines, Communicating, Debugging, Editing, Editing, Editing, Selection, Toxascript, SQL, GI, Linu, Units, Data Engineering, Teat-Orient Development Units, Data Engineering, Teat-Orient Developm

### Experience

Developer 2014-Present

- In Flid data, development for an online marketplace for solar panel installation, built on Spings and deployed on ARS

  I Dissipate, Genetized, and maintained of Spings application for pushing consumer data to solar installer CDMs, e.g. Saledonica

  Flingspate on the Installation of You spin, or an establish, establing resulting and table workflow

  The Spingspate on the Installation of You spin, or an establish, establing resulting and table workflow

  Dissipated invessing of the core commune experience of companing quotes continu, using Budaces and Query

  Dissipated invessing maintains tause for commune, using Purdus and called

  Dissipated in Version maintains tause for commune, using Purdus and called

  The Spingspate of Polipace of Spingspate of Authorities of Leader

  Bull Haddige workflows, exeals, and budge pages to administrat business processes and apport marketing efforts

  Hastly Haddige workflows, exeals, and budge pages to administrat business processes and support marketing efforts

  Hastly Haddige workflows, exeals, and budge pages to administrat business processes and support marketing efforts

  Hastly Haddige workflows, exeals, and called great administration of the support marketing efforts

  Hastly Haddige workflows, exeals, and called great administration of the support marketing efforts

  Haddige and processes and executive control exercises and despit discussors.

### Full Stack Web Developer 2006-Present

IT Operations Manager 2007–2014

Auth-case:

- Natil and managed the <u>legatines</u> useding using the Simuritating OHS, and developed a custom from eard with CSS and Javedorge

- Worde Python scripts to spectrowise the storeth revertey to the website casing, resulting in crossed customer trapplies and feet self-tile.

- Worde EQS queries on Python courts to great the contraction of contracting customer trapplies and feet self-tile.

- White EQS queries on Python courts to great the contracting customer trapplies and customer and barroom analysement.

- Built is guaranteed and the Contraction of the court that the countries of the contraction of the countries of t

Installed, replaced, and adjusted bicycle components and instructed clients on pedal inchinique and posture, resulting in a more comfortable, efficient, and safe experience
 Completed begins defined programs from SEQU, SEQL and Retail
 Relanged custimer residencing by sense; places and appointment
 Ordered and stocked electronics, saddle, nutrition, and media
 Trained add fined columner on electronics

Darwin's Ltd. Cambridge, MA Ordered and stocked raw ingredients and paper goods
 Prepared and served beverages and sandwiches

Software Engineer 2001–2005

- Assumed sole development responsibility for a troubled network device, turning it into a major source of income

   Designed, developed, and documented features for rehearts device using life. Keamilyk, C, C++, Java, and Python
   Designed and deviceped a Plevi who patients for advancted registeries fracting of rehearts, devices

   Conspicted software releases as sole developer and as part of a team
   Tallogated and soldered field lesses in complication with conform terrivices

System Operations Center Operator, Lab Consultant 2000-2002 The Ohio State University Columbus, OH

- Responded to help requests in a Unix and Windows environment
  Designed and developed a graphic FAQ editor in Java
  Provided programming and Unix assistance to students in labs of 50-100 computers

## Grader 1999-2000

Graded papers for an introductory software development course in C++
 Provided guidance for 35-40 students during and outside of class

# Education

Bachelor of Science, Computer & Information Science 2002 The Ohio State University Columbus, OH

Graduated Cum Laude with Honors in the Liberal Arts, 3.640 GPA